Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory10 Mss.B.B61.inventory10
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents O
  - Oetteking, Bruno (Box 67)
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 31; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept.9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept.20; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 May 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 24; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1923 June 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 May 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 June 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - (Enc: Oetteking, Bruno to -Heye, G.Henry Nov. 7, 1925 Henry-Heye, G.H. to Oetteking, Bruno Nov. 9, 1925), 1925 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 July 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927????; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 May 25; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 29; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 June 12; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1929 June 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 June 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 July 17; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1929 July 18; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1929 July 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 July 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Sept.5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 12; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept.15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 15; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 5; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 15; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 22; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept.10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 June 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 16; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 24; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 30; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept.17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 June 28; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1934 July 26; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - Bruno Oetteking -- to R.W. Bryan, 1934 July 26; 2p.
    - Bruno Oetteking -- to C.H.-Heye, 1925 Nov. 7; 2p.
    - (Enc. with Oetteking, Bruno, Nov. 10, 1925)
    - Bruno Oetteking -- to Schreitleitung "Der Angriff", 1932 June 3; 3p.
    - Bruno Oetteking -- from G.H.-Heye, 1925 Nov. 9
    - (Enc. with Oetteking, Bruno, Nov. 10, 1925)
  - Ofleiger, A. (Box 67)
    - To Boas, 1907 July 7
  - O'Flynn, Anna C. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - Anna C. O'Flynn -- to G.E.Stechert & Co., 1923? Jan.; 2p.
  - Ofsevit, Dorothy (Box 67)
    - To Boas, 1940 June 20
    - (see Boas, F. open letter, June 20, 1940)
  - Ogburn, William F. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 June 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 May 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar, 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 May 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept.25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May end; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - William F. Ogburn -- to E.R.Seligman, 1926 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Seligman, E.R., Mar. 31, 1926)
  - Ogden, Robert C. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - Robert C. Ogden -- to F.S.Dellenbaugh, 1927 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Dellenbaugh,F.S., Dec. 23, 1927)
  - Ogden, Rollo (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 17; 1p.
  - O'Hanlon, George (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Apr. 5; 1p.
  - O'Hara, Geoffrey (Box 67)
    - To Boas, 1913 July 31
  - Ohgushi, Toyo (Box 67)
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. end; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. end; 1p.
  - Ohlmarks, Ake (Box 67)
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 15; 1p.
  - Ohsol, J.G. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 29; 1p.
  - Oiticico, Jose (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept.27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 27; 2p.
  - Oko, A.S. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 18; 2p.
  - Olbrechts, Frans M. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Sept.23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 June 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 July 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 May 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 June 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept.21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 May 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 19; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 28; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 June 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 28; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 June 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 July 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Sept.14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 June 25; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 5; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 26; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 July 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 10; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - (ENc. Olbrechts, F.M. to Long,W.W. Apr. 23, 1935), 1935 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Sept.1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Aug. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. end; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 22; 1p.
    - Frans M. Olbrechts -- to C.R.B. Educational Foundation, 1925 Dec. 31; 3p.
    - Frans M. Olbrechts -- to J.W. Fewkes, 1926 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - Frans M. Olbrechts -- to Long, W.W., 1935 Apr. 23; 1p.
  - Oldenberg, Serge d' (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1928 June 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 21; 1p.
  - Oldfather, C.H. (Box 67)
    - (See Boas, F. to Carlson, A.J., July 31, 1941)
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 17; 1p.
  - Oldfather, W.A. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 June 6; 1p.
    - W.A. Oldfather -- to L. Bloomfield, 1926 Nov.?; 2p.
    - (Enc. with Bloomfield, L., Nov. 4, 1926)
  - Oldham, J.H. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 June 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 May 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 14; 2p.
  - Oldman, W.O. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Sept. 6; 1p.
  - Olgin, Moissaye J. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 19; 2p.
  - Oliva, C. (Box 67)
    - G. Oliva -- to Corrado Gini, 1920 July 7; 2p.
  - Oliveira Lima, M. de (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 13; 2p.
  - Oliver, Simeon (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1937 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. end; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. end; 1p.
  - Oliver, Thomas E. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 14
  - Olson, R.L. (Box 67)
    - See Boas, F. to Anon., Dec.,1928
    - R.L.Olson -- to E. Franco, 1933 June end
      (see Uhle, Max)
  - Olson, Willard C. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 6; 1p.
  - O'Mara, Margaret F. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 29; 1p.
  - Oncken, Hermann (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 4; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 July 18; 3p
  - Onis, Federico de (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 19; 1p.
  - Ontario Press (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 15; 1p.
  - Open Court Publishing Co. (Box 67)
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 26
  - Openhym, Wilfred A. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 23; 1p.
  - Open Letter on culture and democracy in Spain. (Box 67)
    - 1933 Dec. end, 15p.
      Filed under Spain. Open letter.
  - Opitz, Mrs. Erna (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 29; 4p.
  - Opler, Marvin K. (Box 67)
    - To Boas, 1940 July 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 July 26; 1p.
  - Oppenheimer, B.S. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 26; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1919 July 12; 1p.
  - Oppenheimer, Ella (Box 67)
    - To Boas, 1923 May 8; 1p.
  - Oppenheimer, J.R. (Box 67)
    - J.R. Oppenheimer -- to F.R.Coudert, 1941 Oct. 13; 1p.
  - Opperman. O. (Box 67)
    - To Boas, 1933 June 29; 3p.
  - Orchi, Pia de (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 17; 1p.
  - Oregon State System of Higher Education (Box 67)
    See Belknap, George N.
  - Oregonian, The (Box 67)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 19; 1p.
  - Orenstein, Lucy (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1939 June 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 2; 1p.
  - Ormes, M.D. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 26; 1p.
  - Orner, A.J. (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 May 11; 1p.
  - Orthovis Company (Box 67)
    See Newman, Montrose
  - Ortiz, Sergio Elias (Box 67)
    - To Boas, 1942 Jan. 10; 1p.
  - O'Roark, L.O. (Box 67)
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 25; 1p.
  - Osborn, Frederick (Box 67)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Sept.20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 June 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Aug. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 June 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept.23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - See Boas,F. to Dunn, L.C., 1937 Oct. 21
    - See Boas,F. to Kallmann, 1937 Oct. 21
    - See Boas,F. to Klineberg, O., 1937 Oct. 21
    - See Boas,F. to MacIver, R.M., 1937 Oct. 21
    - See Boas,F. to Murphy, C., 1937 Oct. 21
    - See Boas,F. to Shapiro, H.L., 1937 Oct. 21
    - See Boas,F. to Todd, T.W., 1937 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - (Enc: Tinney, M.C. to Bertheau,R.C. Feb. 18, 1938), 1938 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 June 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 June 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 June 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Sept.8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 June 27; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. Paper on modern population, 1939 July end
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 13; 1p
    - (Enc: Osborn, F. to Keppel, F.P., 1939 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - Frederick Osborn -- to E.A. Hooten, 1937 Oct. 21
    - (see Boas, F. to Hooten, E.A., Oct. 21, 1937)
    - Frederick Osborn -- to F.P. Keppel, 1939 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - (Enc with Osborn, F., Oct. 13)
    - Frederick Osborn -- from Lorimer, Frank, 1938 Feb. 15
  - Osborn, Henry F. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1905 May 6
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 7
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 28
    - From Boas, 1906 May 11
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept.11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 18
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 11
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 12; 5p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 7
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 June 4
    - From Boas, 1910 June 17
    - From Boas, 1910 June 25
    - From Boas, 1911 June 5
    - From Boas, 1911 June 24; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1911 July 7
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 16
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 18
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 4
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 13
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 7
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 16
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 30
    - From Boas, 1914 Sept.24
    - From Boas, 1915 June 24
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 5
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 11
    - Henry F. Osborn -- from Anon., 1915 Dec. end
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 7
    - From Boas, 1916 Mar. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Mar. 17
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 26
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 31; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 July 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 7; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 May 7; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 June 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 July 25; 1p
    - (Enc: List of material left by Dr. P.E. Goddard), 1928 Sept.15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept.29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Aug. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 May 9
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1906 May 4
    - To Boas, 1906 May 11
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 11
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 June 14
    - To Boas, 1910 June 27
    - To Boas, 1910 June; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 July 11; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 19
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 13
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 29
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 24
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1917 June 15
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 May 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - Henry F. Osborn -- from E.R.A. Seligman, 1917 June 4
    - Henry F. Osborn -- to Stephen P. Duggan, 1920 Apr. 29; 1p.
    - Henry F. Osborn -- to F. M.Warburg, 1913 Dec. 3; 2p.
    - Henry F. Osborn -- from F.M. Warburg, 1913 Dec. 16
    - Henry F. Osborn -- to F.M. Warburg, 1925 Feb. 12; 1p.
  - Osborn, Herbert (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p.
  - Osborn, R.C. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1915 June 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 June 26
  - Osborne, W. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 26
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 6; 2p.
  - Osgood, H.L. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 27
  - Osgood, William F. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 5; 1p.
  - O'Shea, Audrey (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1936 May 21; 1p.
  - Osius, George (Box 68)
    - TO Boas, 1906 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - TO Boas, 1906 Mar. 1; 1p.
  - Osler, William (Box 68)
    - To Boas, undated 1887?; 1p.
    - To Boas, undated 1887?
  - Oslo. Academia Scientiarum Norvigica (Box 68)
    - To Boas, undated
    - (Enc. with Koht, H., May 2, 1926)
  - Oslo. Det Norske Videnskaps-Academi i -- to Conseil International de recherches (Box 68)
    - 1926 Mar. 16, 2p.
    - (Enc. with Koht, H., May 2, 1926)
  - Oslo. Det Norske Videnskaps-Academi i -- to Union Academique internationale (Box 68)
    - 1926 Apr. 26, 3p.
    - (Enc. with Koht, H., May 2, 1926)
  - Olso Institutt for Sammenlignende Kulturforskning (Box 68)
    See Institute for Comparative Research in Human Culture
  - Ossietzky, Carl von (Box 68)
    - See Boas, F. to Flink, S., Sept.12, 1935
  - Ossman, William G. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - William G. Ossman -- to Columbia University, 1930 Apr. 22; 1p.
  - Osswald Garrison Dinner Comm. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 12; 1p.
  - Osten, F.H. von der (Box 68)
    - 1926 May 23, 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 12; 1p.
  - Ostermann. Rev. Joseph D. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1938 May 10; 1p.
  - Osthaus, Carl (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 3; 1p.
  - Ostwald, Wolfgang (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 20; 4p.
    - To Boas, undated; 2p.
  - Osuna, A. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 14; 1p.
  - Otero de, Maria Luisa (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 24
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 1
  - Othoher, B.D. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1915 Sept.15; 1p.
  - Otis, E.O. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 27
  - Ott, Alton H. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - see Boas, F. to Francke, K., 1905 Nov. 28
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 27; 1p.
  - Ottenberg, Reuben (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - (Enc: Ottenberg, R. to Quain, Buell H., Nov. 12,1934)
    - Reuben Ottenberg -- to B.H. Quain, 1934 Nov. 12
    - (Enc. with Ottenberg, Reuben, Nov. 12, 1934)
  - Otto, R. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 10; 1p.
  - Ouarfe, M.M. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 20; 2p.
  - Oubher?,B.H. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1915 June 14; 1p.
  - Ouinones, Pedro G. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1916 Sept.29
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept.27
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 2
  - Oumansky, C. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1939 May 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Sept.8; 1p.
  - Oundjian, A. (Box 68)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 17; 2p.
  - Ousdal, A.P. (Box 68)
    - To Boas, 1928 June 4; 2p.
  - Oustinoff, Mikhael M. (Box 68)